Ukrainian people are like they
людей украинских вот которые как они их
Convinced them that
Убедили в том что
and that's how this Propaganda is like Like you
а вот как вот эта Пропаганда как Типа вы
will travel Convinced What Well Convinced
будете ездить Убедили В чём Ну Убедили в
that Russians are
том что русские
bad Hello Hello I'm from the
плохие Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из
city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from I'm from
города Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я сама из
Crimea And now where is it now unfortunately  in
Крыма А сейчас где сейчас к сожалению в
Moscow, I understood on the stream, if anything And I
Москве понял я на стриме если что А я
understood,
поняла
and what are you talking about?
а вы что вообще о чём разговариваете о
I’m communicating about politics.
политике общаюсь
It’s clear How long ago they left Crimea, that 4
Понятно Как давно из Крыма уехали та 4
months ago, what’s
месяца назад что там
dangerous there? Well, well, no, but there
опасно Да ну ну как бы нет но прилёты
were arrivals, yes. Where were you from in this?  in the Crimea
были да А вы откуда были в этом в Крыму
from Yalta Well, there’s only Usually around
с Ялты Ну там только Обычно по
Sevastopol and here’s Western Crimea Yes
севастополю и вот Западный Крым Да
jinko also Saki Yes
джинко ещё Саки Да вот
Yalta is calm in Yalta there’s nothing
Ялта спокой в Ялте же ничего нету
military so thank God Why is it
военного поэтому Слава богу Зачем оно
there, what to shoot there I understand yes
там надо что туда стрелять понял да у
you have some questions for me
вас ко мне есть какие-то вопросы
and  listen Well, I just caught a man,
а слушайте Ну только что попался мужчина
he says that it’s great that the whole world is
он говорит что классно нам весь мир
helping us We will win Well, the Ukrainian is yours I
помогает Мы выиграем Ну украинский ваш Я
say, who do you think is winning on the battlefield
говорю а как вы считаете на поле боя кто
now Well, some
сейчас вообще побеждают Ну какой-то
nonsense pons I say Okay, good So
ахинею понс я говорю Ладно хорошо Так а
who is winning on the battlefield now  NATO,
кто сечас на поле боя побеждает НАТО
I agree with you.
вот я с вами
You understand that it’s not
согласна Вы же понимаете что это вы не
Ukraine, but NATO and Russia, yes yes yes yes, but
Украина а НАТО с Россией да да да да а
NATO. Well, NATO is an alliance of nuclear powers. It
НАТО Ну НАТО - это союз ядерных держав
can’t
сос яти держав не может
lose. I’m actually surprised, you know what,
проиграть Я вообще удивляюсь знаете чему
when they dropped a bomb on ROSI Nagasaki and
когда скинули на РОСИ нагасаке бомбу и
like  Well, we just threw it out. And what is this
типа ну мы просто скинули А что такого
type to check and Japan is still with them
типа проверить и Япония всё равно с ними
then Good evening Yes, how can you
потом Добрый вечер Да как вы можете
after this I’ll say more than that, uh
после этого я больше того скажу да ээ
Germany and France they fought for how
Германия с Францией они воевали сколько
long. They fought in different ways And they fought together France and
Разно воевали И они вместе Франция с
Britain fought for as long as they did together
британией воевали сколько и они вместе
Britain  they fought with Germany And they and
Британия с Германией воевали И они с
together yes Yeah in Europe in general everyone
вместе да Угу в Европе вообще там все со
fought with everyone there And they somehow together how
всеми воевали И они как-то вместе как
they learned to negotiate Why is
они научились договариваться Почему
Russia like a cattle that can’t come to an agreement with anyone
Россия как быдла с который ни с кем не
and is at war with all its
может договориться и со всеми воюет
neighbors yes And in Europe somehow-  then everyone found a
соседями да А в Европе как-то все нашли
common language, I don’t know, to be honest, it’s
общий язык не знаю честно говоря вот для
also a mystery for me. Well, that is, it turns out that the
меня тоже загадка Ну то есть получается
French and the English were slaughtering each other for
французы и англичане резали друг друга
centuries, the French, the Spaniards, the Spaniards,
столетиями французы Испанцы Испанцы
the English, there, sank each other’s ships.
англичане там топили корабли друг друга
It was just the Dutch, the Germans, everyone there was
Это просто было голландцы немцы там все
just Shiloh. And now they have united and are
там просто Шило А теперь объединились и
like friends.  this is so I have a question for the
дружат как это так У меня вопрос к
American intelligence services or as
американским спецслужбам или как
marketers who are there, I don’t know how
маркетологам кто там я не знаю как
they are Ukrainian people, that’s how they
они людей украинских вот которые как они
convinced them that
их Убедили в том что
and that’s how this Propaganda is like Like you
а вот как вот эта Пропаганда как Типа вы
will travel A Convinced What Well Convinced them
будете ездить А Убедили В чём Ну Убедили
that the Russians  the
в том что русские
bad ones are what you need to drive at them, I’ll
плохие то что нужно на них гнать я
explain, it means I’m like a person who
объясню значит я как человек который
works for American Propaganda, yes,
работает на американскую Пропаганду да
that is,
то есть
my tasks, you don’t write them down, no,
моей задачи мои вы не записываете нет
everything is super, yes, look at
всё супер да вот смотрите в
my ship’s equipment, somehow in Russian, my
мои по судовые обовязки както по-русски
job responsibilities include
должностные обязанности входит промывать
brainwashing the Ukrainians so that they  they didn’t like
мозги украинцам чтобы они не любили
the Russians Why Because I we
россиян Почему Потому что я у нас вот
have some kind of
есть какая-то такая
incomprehensible situation that, for example, a
непонятная ситуация что например
Russian missile flies into Kharkov into a
прилетает ракета Российская в Харьков в
residential building Uh-huh, it kills half the yard, it kills
жилой дом Угу убивает пол двора убивает
small children and People come out and say
маленьких детей а Люди выходят и говорят
We love Russia, we love Russians and my
Мы любим Россию мы любим русских и моя
task is to them  I then arrive at the
задача я им я приезжаю тогда так на
place. So we conduct
место Значит мы идм проводим
conversations, another group psychologically, and we
беседы ещё группа психолого и мы им
begin to explain to them that look at this, a
начинаем объяснять что смотрите это
Russian missile killed your children. You
Российская ракета убила ваших детей Вы
should not like Russia because of this, but that’s what
должны не любить Россию из-за этого а
they are like. No Russia in short
они вот они такие Нет Россия короче
Russia Well done Russia only hits
Россия Молодцы Россия бьёт только по
military facilities like And here I am, I aroused
военным объектам типа И вот я я пробуда
hatred among these people, that is, the task of
ненависть у этих людей то есть задача
people like me is to awaken
таких людей как я мы да пробудить
hatred. Because people seem to be
ненависть Потому что люди как бы вот они
in a state of shock after the missile hit,
в шоковом состоянии после удара ракеты
they don’t quite understand that it was Russia that
они не совсем понимают что это Россия
killed their children, and them and  I explain to them
убила их детей Да и их и я им объясняю
that look, this is Russia, they Russians
что смотрите это Россия они россияне
want your death, they want the death of your
хотят вашей смерти хотят смерти ваших
children, they want to destroy them, but people,
детей они хотят уничтожить вот а люди
like zombies, say no no no
как зомбированный говорят нет нет нет
Russia Well done Russia That’s what I’ll
Россия Молодец Россия Вот и Я вам вот
tell you over the last 2 years, who
что скажу за последние 2 года которые
have been working so intensively, it’s working out very well
работают так интенсивно очень получается
for us  very good results we were able to
у нас очень хорошие результаты мы смогли
Russian-speaking cities there Kharkov Odessa
русскоязычные города там Харьков Одесса
Yes Dnepr Zaporozhye
Да Днепр Запорожье там очень много
spoke a lot of Russian there and like in Crimea and
по-русски говорила да как и в Крыму и
they we raised the degree of hatred towards Russians
они мы градус ненависти к россиянам
in Russian-speaking cities
подняли именно в русскоязычных городах
now the latest sociology
сейчас вот последняя социология
was carried out Yes the Razumkov center then in
проводилась Да центром разумкова то в
Kharko the
Харько
level of hatred  towards Russians is higher than
уровень ненависти к россиянам выше чем
in Lviv, that is, in Lvov Yes, the level of
во Львове то есть во Львове Да уровень
hatred towards Russians is only
ненависти к россиянам всего
14.88 about This can be said tolerantly
14,88 про Это толерантно можно сказать
Here in Kharkov in Kharkov Yes,
Вот в Харькове в Харькове Да
94% of the population of Kharkov hates Russians
94% населения Харькова ненавидит россиян
before the start of the war, there was only 1% and I will say
до начала войны был только 1% и я скажу
this shows
это показывает
that the hall  we get the American State Department for
что зала американского госдепа мы
a reason, we were able to Well, it’s
получаем не зря мы смог Ну вот это
true that they say that it’s stupid to manage
правда говорят что вот управлять тупыми
Yes, it’s much easier, here’s a
Да это намного проще вот человек
reasonable person, he
разумный он
’ll blow it up Don’t hang up Hello, you can hear Dada,
задует не Зависай Алло слышно Дада
something
что-то
was hanging up, you told him, he told him,
зависало вы ему наговорили наговорили он
but here it’s illogical, that’s it
а вот тут нелогично так вот именно Да
Yes, look  I was still studying at the
вот смотрите я ещ вот когда учился в
university. Yes, in the American university we were
университете Да в американском вот нас
taught as a special technique of
учили как специальное техники
psychological influence on a person.
психологического воздействия на личность
Yes, they explained that it is easier to control stupid people
Э да объясняли что тупыми управлять
and therefore showed an example that, for
легче и поэтому показывали пример что
example, in Russia, yes, Putin has been ruling in Russia since
вот например в России да вот в России с
1999. Yeah,
девяносто девятого года правит Путин Угу
that is, the Americans  they said this in the 21st
то есть американцы говорили это на в XXI
century now, yes The most important thing is that they
веке сейчас да Самое вот феномен они
say that this is a kind of
говорят что такая вроде как страна
rich country, but it is populated by such stupid
богатая Но населена такими тупыми
individuals and they are so easy to control,
индивидами и ими так легко управлять
there are a lot of stupid people, yes, very, very many
очень много тупых Да очень-очень много
stupid people, yes, and in Ukraine, you see, it’s
тупых да А в Украине Понимаете вот тут
very difficult to work with them here  because
очень сложно с ними работать потому что
they are they Yes, they need to be directly
они они Да их нужно прямо
reprogrammed I give them the program
перепрограммировать я им даю программу
Let’s hate the Russians they No don’t
Давайте ненавидеть россиян они Нет не
listen but you yourself, as a
слушайте а вам вот самому как
Russian speaker, don’t, well, it’s not offensive that
русскоязычному вам не ну не обидно что
America
вот Америка
wants America constantly puts sticks in
хочет Америка постоянно вставляет палки
Russia That is, she is also an ambassador Well,
России То есть она ещё и посола Ну да
look I  I’m not Russian-speaking, I’m
смотрите я не русскоязычный я
Ukrainian-speaking, and I, in principle, uh Well,
украиноязычный да и я в принципе ээ Ну
not that I’ll say I don’t condemn America, I
не то что я скажем Не осуждаю Америку я
praise how it will be in Russian, I approve of
схвалюю как это будет по-русски одобряю
its actions Yes, I think that it
её действия Да я считаю что она мало
puts few sticks
палок вставляет
in the wheels of Russia Well, I wouldn’t say
в как бы колёса России Ну я б не сказал
that America  we quarreled, you know,
что Америка нас поссорила понимаете
because America is far away and we are not close to
потому что Америка далеко а мы близко не
America, for example, well, if America It
Америка например ну если Америка Мне
seems to me, after all, that this is ours Yes,
кажется вот всё-таки Что вот это сво Да
and the seizure of Crimea, remember when the
и захват Крыма это вот помните когда
seizure of Crimea Who was
хват Крыма Кто был в Америке
President Biden in America like Obama Obama was
президент байден вроде Обама Обама был
oh Obama Yes so  Look, Obama,
ой Обама Да так вот смотрите Обама вот
what he did, they forced Putin to
он что сделал они заставили Путина
attack Crimea Yeah, because Putin
напасть на Крым Угу потому что Путина
was forced, but Putin couldn’t just
заставили но не мог же Путин просто
attack Crimea Donetsk Lugansk And
взять напасть на Крым Донецк Луганск А
now he was provoked into attacking the whole of Ukraine like
теперь ещё напасть так на всю Украину
that, no, he was simply
его спровоцировали на это нет его просто
forced Well, he can’t  w ee
заставили Ну не может он ж ээ
Such an independent adult man, they
Независимый такой взрослый человек его
couldn’t provoke him against America.
не могли спровоцировать на амери А вот
But look, America, they need the destruction of
да смотри Америка им нужно уничтожение
the Slavs, you understand, because you know
славян понимаете потому что вы знаете
the concept of the golden billion. If you
концепцию золотого миллиарда Если Вы
look at what you hear, Yes, the fact is that
посмотрите что слыша Да дело в том что
if the level of the World Ocean rises
если уровень Мирового океана поднимется
another meter, Yes, half of America  everything will be
ещё на метр Да половина Америки будет
under water, look, all of America, yes,
под водой вся смотрите вся Америка да
this is the coast, yes, cities on the coasts,
это побережье Да города на побережьях
Europe, all cities on the coasts or on
Европа все города на побережьях либо на
large rivers, if
больших реках если поднимается сейчас
the melting of Arctida is rising now. They know that
таяние Арктида Они же знают что сейчас
we are now experiencing global warming and there are
идёт у нас потепление глобальное и есть
forecasts that in 10 years the water level will
прогнозы Что за 10 лет уровень воды
rise by a meter  up to three World
поднимется от метра до трёх Мирового
Oceans, that is, uh, all this crowd of people will
океана то есть э все этой толпе народа
need to move somewhere, what are they
нужно будет куда-то переселяться они что
doing, they specifically want to exterminate the
делают они специально хотят истребить
Slavs Yes, with the hands of the Slavs, that is, they
славян Да руками славян то есть они
forced Putin Putin is not a Slav, you
заставили Путина Путин же не славянин вы
can see him in his face, it’s clear that
видите его по его лицу это однозначно да
he is of
он а
unknown origin  yes But let’s say
непонятного происхождения да Но скажем
these are not Slavic facial features Well, you’ve
это не славянские черты лица Ну вот вы
seen a lot of Slavs, yes you lived
видели славян очень много да вы жили
among the Slavs, it’s clear that he’s not Slavic by his
среди славян видно что он не славян по
behavior by facial expressions by anthropological
поведению по мимике по антропологическом
type and with his help Yes, it’s the Slavs that are being killed
типу и с помощью его Да убивают именно
Look Putin is destroying
славян Посмотрите Путин уничтожает
Russian-speaking cities Mariupol bakhmut
русскоязычные города Мариуполь бахмут
Kharkov Yes this  Russian-speaking people, that is, uh, and
Харьков Да это русскоязычные то есть э и
this territory, uh, maybe
вот эту территорию э де в том может
they read this concept in the CIA, it was
читали такую концепция в ЦРУ было
developed
разработано
called the Neo Golden Horde, not without hearing
называется Нео Золотая Орда не не слыша
it. The fact is that after the settlement of these
вот Дело в том что по заселению вот этих
steppes, Kherson region Crimea Donetsk
степей Херсонская область Крым Донецкая
region Krasnodar region, all these
область Краснодарский край вот эти все
steppes will be populated  by these
степи будут заселяться этими
settlers from America during the flood,
переселенцами из Америки во время потопа
that is, they will be called the Golden
да то есть они будут называться Золотая
Horde, this is the concept of the New new, in
Орда это концепция такой Ново новое
short, global government will be. That’s
короче глобальное правительство будет
why they are now clearing, they are
Вот и поэтому они сейчас расчищают они
specially shelling Kharkov so that
специально обстреливают Харьков чтобы
millions of Kharkov will leave and leave. They will go to
миллионы Харьков уехал да уехали Они в
Poland somewhere. Yes, there are a lot of Kharkov residents
Польшу куда-то Да очень много харьковчан
now in Europe they
сейчас в Европе они теперь европейцами
are now becoming Europeans and you understand what
стают и вы же понимаете А что такое
Europe is Yes, it’s already there Boy with a
Европа Да это уже и там Мальчик с
boy and all that stuff Well, yes, Well, I
мальчиком и всякое такое Ну да то Ну мне
don’t like what you know, here they are, I
не нравится то что знаете вот они я
identify myself as a pot there, like I
идентифицирую себя как горшок там типа я
can change the gender  And then here they are. Well,
могу и пол поменять И то ещё вот они Ну
as if you know, they are exterminating their People with
как будто бы знаете свой Народ же
all this. Well,
истребляют вот этим всем Да так вот
look, and it turns out that Putin is
смотрите и получается Путин специально
bombing Kharkov on purpose. So that people go there,
бомбит Харьков Да чтобы люди выезжали
they go there to Poland, to America,
они выезжают там в Польшу в Америку
to Britain, and right away
в Британию и сразу
I just have a friend from Kharkov
вот у меня просто знакомая с Харькова
Yes, as soon as she crossed the border
есть Да она как только переехала границу
with Poland, she and the children
с Польшей она с детьми
were Polish, this border guard is standing
была польский этот пограничник стоит
there, the social teacher immediately Bert
м социальный педагог сразу Берт детей
registers them for how many years, why have they been
оформляет их Сколько лет что так
asking what genders you are in? They
спрашивают каких вы гендеров у детей
write it down on a sign, and it’s written not by mom,
записывают в табличку и её пишут не мама
but by pant
а пант
[music]
[музыка]
one parent parent  she sends me one,
один родитель родитель один она мне
says
присылает говорит
Andrey, they told me I’m no longer a
Андрей они мне уже я уже не
mother there, there are no mothers there, and you know why
мама там нету мам там и знаете почему
this is Pan o and Pan 2, they are
вот это Пан о и Пан 2 они
preparing a transition in some, it hangs a
готовят переход в некоторых зависает
little, didn’t even
немножко не даже
say, but I have something peak there Yes, but to the
сказал а у меня что-то там пик Да но
right, they are stupid to drive
направо тупыми управлять
It’s easier I didn’t tell you enough Yes,
легче Я я же недо рассказал Да что дате
I’ll tell the date before that they are preparing Pan o
я уже до расскажу что этим готовят Пан о
Pan 2 so that later there will be a parent panche and
Пан 2 чтобы потом было парент панче да
multi antler families will do for children
мульти пантовые семьи будут делать детям
Yes, subscribe to my Telegram right now, the
Да подпишись на мий Telegram прямо зараз
axis of wine and
ось вин а
popk is more and more important YouTube Zaga
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through srg org in your ban and even
нас через срг ор в твий бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people sometimes I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need Mali to write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video sche tezh tsikava and korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will give you trima sing
информация и мы пон вами трима пой
operational connection is not important in that chi
оперативный звязок незалежно в того чи
show you about it YouTube Glory to Ukraine
покаже вам про це YouTube Слава Украине
letter
пись